<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TranslationPack>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part0">
        <Translation language="English">
            Welcome to Timed!
            This Tutorial will teach you how to play Timed.
            So don't waste anymore time, touch this field to continue ...
        </Translation>
        <Translation language="German">
            Willkommen bei Timed!
            Dieses Tutorial wird dir alles beibringen was du zum spielen von Timed brauchst.
            Also verschwenden wir lieber keine weiter Zeit, berühre dieses Feld um weiter zu machen ...
        </Translation>
    </Translations>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part1">
        <Translation language="English">
            This is the timeline. It is simular to a videoplayer. 
            It does not only show the current time, but you can also use it to change the time. 
            Touch this field to continue ...</Translation>
        <Translation language="German">XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</Translation>
    </Translations>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part2">
        <Translation language="English">
            Pressing this button will result in the game to continue.
            When doing so the icon will change and pressing it again will halt the game.
            Start and then pause the game using the button to continue ...
        </Translation>
        <Translation language="German">XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</Translation>
    </Translations>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part3">
        <Translation language="English">
            As you might have already notices, stoping the game will popup 5 additional buttons.
            Those can be used to finetune the time in microsteps.
            Try them all out and when you are finished press the upper button, 
            which will reset the time to 0, to continue ...
        </Translation>
        <Translation language="German">XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</Translation>
    </Translations>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part4">
        <Translation language="English">
            Alright, that was enought about the UI for now.
            The games goal is to get the required amount of balls into the goal.
            The amount is different for every level and is marked by the number in its center.
            Touch this field to continue ...
        </Translation>
        <Translation language="German">XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</Translation>
    </Translations>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part5">
        <Translation language="English">
            This is the already mentioned ball, or rather ColliderBody.
            As you might have already noticed when playing around with the video player it is 
            effected by the normal gravity. However because of the flat ground the ColliderBody
            won't get anywhere near the goal.
            Touch this field to continue ...
        </Translation>
        <Translation language="German">XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</Translation>
    </Translations>
    <Translations tag="TutorialBasic0Part6">
        <Translation language="English">
            Thats where the so called Effectors will get handy. As the name might already tell
            they can effect the ColliderBodys that get into their range. When a ColliderBody
            is in their Range its core will get bigger indicating that it could interact 
            with the in Range ColliderBody.
            Pause the time, reset it with the Resetbutton, play it again and see how
            the Effectors core will get bigger. Afterwards touch this field to continue ...
        </Translation>
        <Translation language="German">XXXXXXXXXXXXXX</Translation>
    </Translations>
</TranslationPack>